

- +90 535 457 72 40
- hicaku.com/
- github.com/Spencehiko

Summary

Passionate student of intriguing subjects.

Open to new ideas and willing to use my skills combined with well-thought projects.

Building CMSs and Websites since 2018.

Worked both in a start-up, a normal sized company and a global company. So I know every struggle, every challenge that companies face, no matter how big they are.

Looking forward to taking my current skills to upper levels and benefit both myself and the company I am working for.

Work experience

Frontend Engineer

06/2021 - NOW

Huawei

Currently I am working in Huawei as an assistant software engineer and mainly focused on frontend development. We developed several tools on Petal Maps. Although we had a small team of developers, we managed to overcome tough obstacles on our way. I won a Future Star Award at the end of 2021.

Tech Stack: Vue.js, Typescript, HTML, CSS(LESS), Jest, Cypress, Git, Sourcetree

Junior Full Stack Web Developer

12/2018 - 05/2021

Firmasoft Information Technologies

In Firmasoft, the aim was to build CMSs, websites and mobile apps for our clients. I developed many websites and CMSs with our small team. I worked full-time on holidays and part-time on the rest.

Tech Stack: PHP, HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, MySQL, Dreamweaver

Junior Frontend Developer

06/2018 - 11/2018

Datapare Information Technologies

I learnt basics of web development and working in a fast paced, agile team. It was a startup and I worked full-time on holidays and part-time on the rest.

Tech Stack: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Vue.js

Education

Graduate 2016 - 2021

Istanbul Technical University - Mathematics Engineering

GPA: 2.97

Skills

Vue.js

I have been working with Vue.js for my current company and also I am developing personal apps to improve myself. At work we use Vuex and in my personal projects I use Pinia with Composition API.

Javascript

I have been working on this subject for over 4 years and I have built global scale projects with it in my previous job experiences.

TypeScript

I have been working with TypeScript implemented in Vue.js.

HTML5 & CSS3 (+ LESS)

For many years, I have worked with HTML and CSS. I have a really good understanding of the correlation between them and I can code a design for the web page easily. I know LESS as well.

Tailwind CSS

I am using Tailwind CSS in my personal projects and I have built several apps with it.

Github

I have simple knowledge of Git commands. (push, pull, merge etc.) I have been using Sourcetree to visualize these actions, but I can use them on command line as well.

PHP & MySQL

I have been working with PHP for over 2 years and I have built several CMSs with it. I am familiar with OOP and API structures of PHP.

Testing Tools

I used Jest for unit testing and Cypress for end-to-end testing. I have the basic knowledge of them.

Languages

English

I can explain myself confidently in any situation fluently.

Chinese

I am a beginner in Chinese and I really find it intriguing.

Hobbies

- Video Games
- Teaching Mathematics and Geometry
- Photography
- Sports
- Books (Sci-Fi, Historical, War, Science)

References

Serkan Uz - CEO and Founder of Datapare Information Technologies

serkanuz@datapare.com

Mustafa Tunç - CEO and Founder of Firmasoft Information Technologies

mustafatunc@firmasoft.com

Salih Kesepara - Team Leader of Petal Maps Frontend Team at Huawei R&D

salih.kesepara@huawei.com